vanitynoapologies.com 2017-05-23

# Privacy Policy|Vanitynoapologies|Indian Makeup and Beauty Blog

The privacy of our visitors to vanitynoapologies.com is important to us.  We recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit us, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

(a) Collection of Information.  We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors.  For example, mailing information is required to award giveaway prizes to winners, but this information is never used or sold for any additional purpose beyond fulfilling the prize.  Personally identifiable information is used solely to address your specific request and is not sold to third parties or market researchers.

(b) Distribution of Information.  We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.

(c) Commitment to Data Security.  Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.

(d) Children.  We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received Personal Information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our records.
